Rob Kirby Front end developer

Ж

About

I'm a front end developer with six years commercial experience, working with high profile digital agencies in the North West.

I'm interested in modular and performant front end development, and crafting engaging user experiences.

Contact

Links

- rkirby.co.uk
- in linkedin.com/in/robwkirby/
- ⇔ codepen.io/RobKirby/
- github.com/robwkirby

Certifications

Umbraco Certified Developer Level 1

Skills

HTML, CSS (SASS, LESS), CSS Architecture (BEM), JavaScript (jQuery, Vue.js, React), Git, npm, Yarn, Gulp, Grunt, Webpack, Wordpress, Umbraco

Tools

VScode, Github, Bitbucket, Jira, Browserstack, Litmus, Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects), Invision, Zeplin

Work Experience

2015 - Now O Senior Front End Developer, Soap Media

Front end development on PHP based sites (Wordpress & Symfony). Responsibilities include mentoring junior staff, creating and maintaining a reusable front end workflow for the dev team, and informing the hiring process.

2013 - 2015 🖕 Front End Developer, Fat Media

Front end development on ASP (primarily .NET MVC) and PHP based sites as part of the Digital Production team. Work included fully responsive site builds with CMS integration and maintenance / support work.

2012 - 2013 👌 Assistant Graphic Designer, Fat Media

Design work on components for existing websites using Photoshop and Illustrator.

Education

2009 - 2012 O University of Central Lancashire

BSc (Hons) Web & Multimedia (Grade 2:1)